searates.com 2007-05-29

# Privacy policy

Home > Privacy policy

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on SeaRates and affiliated websites. 

On some pages you can order products, subscriptions or memebrships, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: name, company name, address, e-mail address, telephone, fax.

We use session cookies to give you access to member's area. Session cookie is deleted when your browser is closed. We use cookies to get attendance statistics of our site. Cookies that are set by our site cannot be read by other sites. We can use information that is collected by our web server for administrative purposes only. We do not collect nor store customer's credit card information on our site. 

If you communicate with us using the e-mail addresses provided in the different sections of our website or using contact form, your e-mail address or any additional contact information will be used to contact you to send the information requested or to send information about related services. 

You can access your personally identifiable information that was entered in registration form by entering your login and password. You can correct factual errors in your personal identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

User inquries can be passed to the insurance and forwarding companies in accordance with the freight exchange rules. 

When you subscribe for e-mail updates, we provide you with information of your interest periodically. You may also receive information about our products or services if you have chosen to. You can unsubscribe by contacting us or changing the subscription status by logging in to your personal area with your user name and password. 

Some links on SeaRates may link to third party websites. These websites are owned by their respective companies and their privacy policies may differ from ours. We encourage you to be aware of their privacy policies before providing them with personally identifiable information. 

SeaRates reserves the right to modify or amend this policy at any time without prior notice. 

Feel free to contact us with any questions you may have. 

* * *
